https://www.mersino.com/about/privacy-policy.php

Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
; To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
; To send periodic emails
The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.
Do we use cookies?
We do not use cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicin g you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
This policy was last modified on 2/20/13
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
Website:
www.mersino.com
Address:
10162 E. Coldwater Rd.
Davison, Michigan 48423, US
Email:
register@mersino.com
Phone:
Mersino's manufacturer, Global Pump, has developed a cutter solution for severe ragging and clog...
Read More...
Waterford, Michigan Emergency Sinkhole
Mersino is onsite in Waterford, Michigan responding to a 54" sewer collapse due to a sinkhole. ...
Read More...
Midland, Michigan Flood Relief
Mersino is onsite in Midland, Michigan to aid in the flood relief efforts from the breach of the Ede...
Read More...
